Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V. Academic Career and Events
  - "Catch Up" Video Installation Version, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_312)
    The cassette's label notes that the video installation was at Serpentine Galleries in London.
  - Class on Music at Newcastle, Conducted with Stuart Marshall, Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_362, Audiocassette 267_265)
  - Dawana Reading, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_319)
  - Halifax Convention, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_318)
  - [Illegible] Ex Habitable with Ellis, Roosevelt Island, Etc., Undated (Box 23, 16mm film reels 267_095)
  - Institute for the Future Notes, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_306)
  - "It Doesn't Sound Like Me" Video Installation Version, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_312)
  - Lecture on Photography - Newcastle, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_323)
  - Notes - Full Explanation?, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_213)
  - RISD English Class, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_242)
  - Stewart Hannon - Political Tactics and Defense Strategy, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_282)
  - Speech Tape, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_286)
  - Susan Grant Interview, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_311)
- Hard Drive (Box 26, Disk FA-MSS-267-1)
- Floppy Disks (Box 26, Disk FA-MSS-267-2, FA-MSS-267-3)
- CDs and DVDs (Box 28, Box 29, Box 30)